fcebook.com 2006-12-05

# Whos On MySpace? Free Myspace tracker! Myspace Spy Space Profile Snoop Counter

**Privacy Policy**

This statement discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices of WhosonMySpace, pertinent to this web site. This statement supplements our Legal Notices, with respect to privacy. The terms, conditions and provisions of our Legal Notices shall govern and take precedence over any conflicting provision or disclosure in this privacy statement. 

Purpose: 

WhosonMySpace.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for WhosonMySpace.com. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our web site, and statistics gathering for reporting to members of this website. Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their first name and or email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. It is our general policy to use contact information, (such as e-mail address, first name and zip code) for internal purposes and to not sell or otherwise provide this information to third parties. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary with updates regarding WhosonMySpace.com. 

Security: 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All data is encrypted and kept in a secure facility. This site has security measures in place to help protect the information under its control from loss, misuse and alteration. 

IP Addresses: 

Your IP address is captured when you visit this site. It is used to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer the web site, to track the IP origin of abusive behavior, or track the IP origin of an unlawful activity, such as an attempt to violate the web site's security. This information may be shared with third parties, such as law enforcement agencies with respect to unlawful activities and Internet service providers. 

Third Parties: 

Except as otherwise disclosed in this privacy statement, your personally identifiable information is not shared with any third party. For example, we do not sell, or otherwise give third parties access to, our customer list. 

Corrections/Updates: 

To make any changes in your contact information, please contact us. Please do not send us any sensitive information via email.
